[
    {
      "id": 1,
      "correct-answer": 2,
      "question": "Which large town, other than Napier, was extensively destroyed by the 1931 Hawkes Bay earthquake?",
      "answer1": "Auckland",
      "answer2": "Hastings",
      "answer3": "Ormiston",
      "answer4": "Invercargill"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "correct-answer": 1,
      "question": "What is the southernmost <b>town</b> in the South Island?",
      "answer1": "Bluff",
      "answer2": "Hastings",
      "answer3": "Christchurch",
      "answer4": "Auckland"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "correct-answer": 3,
      "question": "How many million years ago did dinosaurs become extinct <b>in NZ</b>?",
      "answer1": "5",
      "answer2": "35",
      "answer3": "65",
      "answer4": "100"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "correct-answer": 2,
      "question": "In 1918 many people died in NZ - from what illness?",
      "answer1": "Bubonic plague",
      "answer2": "Flu",
      "answer3": "Mumps",
      "answer4": "Meningitis"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "correct-answer": 1,
      "question": "What is Stan Walker best known for?",
      "answer1": "Singing",
      "answer2": "Dancing",
      "answer3": "Vlogging",
      "answer4": "Inventing"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "correct-answer": 1,
      "question": "The tui, stitchbird and bellbird eat mainly what?",
      "answer1": "Nectar",
      "answer2": "Breadcrumbs",
      "answer3": "Chips",
      "answer4": "Other birds"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "correct-answer": 1,
      "question": "Which West Coast natural resource did Thomas Brunner discover?",
      "answer1": "Coal",
      "answer2": "Moa bones",
      "answer3": "Kiwis",
      "answer4": "Gold"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "correct-answer": 3,
      "question": "In what year did Jean Batten fly solo from England to NZ?",
      "answer1": "1806",
      "answer2": "1916",
      "answer3": "1936",
      "answer4": "1966"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "correct-answer": 3,
      "question": "Which language became an official language of NZ in 1987?",
      "answer1": "English",
      "answer2": "NZ Sign Language",
      "answer3": "Maori",
      "answer4": "Samoan"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "correct-answer": 4,
      "question": "What is the name for a Maori priest?",
      "answer1": "Iwi",
      "answer2": "Ratana",
      "answer3": "Tangata",
      "answer4": "Tohunga"
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "correct-answer": 1,
      "question": "Which town was once called Kororareka and in 1840 was the largest settlement in New Zealand?",
      "answer1": "Russell",
      "answer2": "Auckland",
      "answer3": "Hamilton",
      "answer4": "Christchurch"
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "correct-answer": 3,
      "question": "What historic shipment first took place in 1882, marking the start of important exports from NZ?",
      "answer1": "The first shipment of milk",
      "answer2": "The first shipment of animals",
      "answer3": "The first shipment of frozen meat",
      "answer4": "The first shipment of oil"
    },
    {
      "id": 13,
      "correct-answer": 3,
      "question": "How many years is it since a volcano has erupted in Auckland?",
      "answer1": "10",
      "answer2": "100",
      "answer3": "600",
      "answer4": "1600"
    },
    {
      "id": 14,
      "correct-answer": 3,
      "question": "Interisland ferries operate between which city and town in the North and South Islands?",
      "answer1": "Auckland and Invercargill",
      "answer2": "Auckland and Picton",
      "answer3": "Wellington and Picton",
      "answer4": "Hamilton and Christchurch"
    },
    {
      "id": 15,
      "correct-answer": 4,
      "question": "Which place is known as the 'Sunshine Capital' of New Zealand? It usually averages more sunshine hours than anywhere else.",
      "answer1": "Auckland",
      "answer2": "Christchurch",
      "answer3": "Hamilton",
      "answer4": "Blenheim"
    },
    {
      "id": 16,
      "correct-answer": 1,
      "question": "In New Zealand slang, what is a 'prang'?",
      "answer1": "A minor vehicle accident",
      "answer2": "A mistake",
      "answer3": "A pool",
      "answer4": "A cable"
    },
    {
      "id": 17,
      "correct-answer": 4,
      "question": "Who was the leader of the National Party in the 2017 election?",
      "answer1": "Simon Bridges",
      "answer2": "Judith Collins",
      "answer3": "Jacinda Ardern",
      "answer4": "Bill English"
    },
    {
      "id": 18,
      "correct-answer": 4,
      "question": "Which is the driest main city in NZ?",
      "answer1": "Invercargill",
      "answer2": "Wellington",
      "answer3": "Hamilton",
      "answer4": "Christchurch"
    },
    {
      "id": 19,
      "correct-answer": 2,
      "question": "Geothermal power generates what percentage of NZ's electricity?",
      "answer1": "None",
      "answer2": "20%",
      "answer3": "25%",
      "answer4": "55%"
    },
    {
      "id": 20,
      "correct-answer": 2,
      "question": "In which year were the first Maori MPs elected to Parliament?",
      "answer1": "1853",
      "answer2": "1868",
      "answer3": "1893",
      "answer4": "1903"
    }
]